Guide to the F. Curtis Michel Scientist-Astronaut Papers, 1951-1981 MS 043
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II. NASA Papers, c. 1963-1981, 230181; 65 boxes
  - Subseries L: Apollo Program, 230370
    - Sub-subseries 5: Experiments by Number, 230412
      - S-21: Airglow Horizon Photography, June 1965; 230420 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - S-22: Low Z Cosmic Ray, April-June 1965; 230419 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - S-23: High Z Cosmic Ray, June 1965; 230418 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - S-25: Infra-red IR Temperature Sounding of Earth's Atmosphere, July 1965; 230417 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - S-26: Ion Wake Measurement, September 1965; 230416 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Description of Experiments for Apollo Flights SA-204, SA-205 and SA-207, December 1, 1965; 230415 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - 507 (211) Flight Mission Description, with list of experiments, September 13, 1965; 230414 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - X-Experiments: X-15: Physiological Effects of Low Magnetic Fields During Space Flight, n.d.; 230413 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Work Group on Apollo Experiments and Training on the Scientific Aspects of Apollo Program, December 15, 1963; 230411 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - AES [Apollo Extension System] Experiment Program Discussions Presentation Charts, May 12, 1965; 230410 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Experiments and Instrumentation for Scientific Investigation of the Moon (ALSS), June 28, 1965; 230409 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Apollo Service Module Experiments Assembly (ASMEA) Request for Proposal, July 20, 1965; 230408 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Study of Manned Space Investigations in X and Gamma Ray Astronomy, January 1, 1966; 230407 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Briefing Charts, Lunar Orbital Survey Missions (LOSM), January 11, 1966; 230406 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Northrop Review, Apollo Experiments Pallet Program, January 20, 1966; 230405 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Manned Experiment Program: Opportunities for International Participation, February 6, 1966; 230404 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Program Review Material, Experiment Integration Working Group Progress Review, AEP Program, March 15, 1966; 230403 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Overall Mission Operations Plan for Apollo Experiments Pallet (handout for monthly review), March 16, 1966; 230402 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Handbook for the Goddard Experiment Package, September 1, 1967; 230401 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries 6: Apollo Applications Program [AAP], 230383
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, 1965-1966; 230400 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, September 1966-April 1967; 230399 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, April 1966-April 1967; 230398 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, May 1967; 230397 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, June-December, 1967; 230396 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Apollo Applications Program Correspondence, 1968; 230395 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Apollo Applications Program and Science, February-April 1966, n.d.; 230394 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Apollo Applications Program Experiment General Requirements, March 15, 1968; 230393 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Apollo Applications Program Experiments, June-October 1966; 230392 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Apollo Applications Program Mission Planning Task Force, November 1965-January 1966; 230391 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Apollo Applications Program Flight Operations Plan Meetings, 230384
        - January-March 1967, 230390 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - April-May 1967, 230389 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - June-July 1967, 230388 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - September-November 1967, 230387 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - March-May 1968, 230386 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - June-September 1968, 230385 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 7: Apollo Applications Program - General Files, 230371
      - Apollo Applications Program Study of Utilization of LM [Lunar Module], Grumman Progress Reports for January-April 1967, 230382 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Flight Mission Directive for AAP-3/AAP-4, March 27, 1967; 230381 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Reference Flight Plan, AAP-1/AAP-2, June 1, 1967, April 5, 1968; 230380 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Preliminary Data Specification Document for Missions AAP 1a, 1/2, and 3/4, June 1967; 230379 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - GAEC [Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation] Biweekly Reports, July-October 1967; 230378 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - AAP-3/AAP-4 Flight Crew Experiments Guide, March 11, 1968; 230377 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Radiation Characteristics of Photographic Film for Use in Apollo Application Experiments, June 30, 1967; 230376 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - CSM Requirements and Configuration for AAP Flights 1 through 4, July 21, 1967; 230375 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - AAP/LM-A Alternate Study Reports (2 volumes, 1-18, 19-21), September and November 1967; 230374 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - AAP/LM-A ATM Controls and Display Console Configuration Review, November 15, 1967; 230373 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - AAP/LM-A Configuration Freeze, Reports (2 volumes), November 16, 1967; 230372 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Subseries M: Surveyor Program, 230351
    - Surveyor Project: Lunar Scientific Model, August 3, 1965; 230369 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Surveyor III Preliminary Science Results, May 15, 1967; 230368 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Surveyor III: A Preliminary Report, June 1967; 230367 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Surveyor III Mission Report, Part II: Scientific Results Addendum, September 1, 1967; 230366 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Surveyor III Mission Report, Part III: Television Data, November 10, 1967; 230365 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Surveyor V: A Preliminary Report, December 1967; 230364 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Surveyor V Mission Report, Part I: Mission Description and Performance, March 15, 1968; 230363 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Surveyor VII Mission Report, Part II: Science Results, March 15, 1968; 230362 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Surveyor VI: A Preliminary Report, March 1968; 230361 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Surveyor VII: A Preliminary Report, May 1968; 230360 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index of Surveyor Scientific Publication and Presentations, Jet Propulsion Laboratory, June 1, 1968; 230359 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Report on Surveyor Project (Reprint, Journal of Geophysical Research), June 15, 1968); 230358 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Surveyor Project Final report, Part II: Science Results, June 15, 1968; 230357 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Lunar, Surface Thermal Characteristics During Eclipse from Surveyors III, V and after Sunset from Surveyor V (AIAA Paper, presented at conference, June 24-26, 1968); 230356 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Surveyor V Mission Report, Part III: Television Data, July 15, 1968; 230355 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Surveyor VI Mission Report, Part I: Mission Description and Performance, September 15, 1968; 230354 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Report on Surveyor 5 Project (Reprint, Journal of Geophysical Research), November 15, 1968); 230353 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Surveyor VII Mission Report, Part I. Mission Description and Performance, February 15, 1969; 230352 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Subseries N: Space Station Program, 230326
    - Space Stations - Correspondence, 1965-66; 230350 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Condensed Study, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230349 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Sections 1 & 2: Introduction, Technical Summary, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230348 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Section 3: Modular Space Station Design Part I, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230347 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Section 3: Modular Space Station Design Part II, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230346 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Section 4: Preliminary Specifications, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230345 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Sections 5 & 6: Applications & Development Plan, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230344 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Modular Multipurpose Space Station Study, Appendix, Expermiental Application Summary, Lockheed, July 30, 1965; 230343 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - ORL [Orbital Research Laboratory] Experiment Program, Volume A, Framework fro Synthesis, February 21, 1966 Condensed Summary, 230342 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Beyond AAP, March-April 1966; 230341 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - November 9-10 AMMP/OSSA Meeting [Advanced Manned Mission Program] [Office of Space Science and Applications], October-November 1966; 230340 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Advanced Missions, September 1965-June 1967; 230339 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Study of Multipurpose Mission Module, October, 1965; 230327
      - Baseline Design, Volume 1, 230338 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Baseline Design, Volume 2, 230337 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Costs, 230336 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Design Data Book, 230335 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Electrical Power and Environmental Control Subsystems, 230334 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Mockup, 230333 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Phase C Work Statement, 230332 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Program Plan, 230331 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Summary (Earth Orbit), 230330 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Summary (Lunar Orbit), 230329 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Utilization of the Multipurpose Mission Module, 230328 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Subseries O: Technical and Scientific Publications, 230237
    - On the Generalized Theory, Scientific American, April 1950; 230325 (Box 59)
    - Chemical Analysis by Infrared, Scientific American, October 1953; 230324 (Box 59)
    - Scanning Techniques in Biology and Medicine, Scientific American, June 5, 1962; 230323 (Box 59)
    - Studies of Micrometeorites Obtained from a Recoverable Sounding Rocket, Scientific American, 1962; 230322 (Box 59)
    - Flying Spot Television Microscopy, 1963; 230321 (Box 59)
    - Models for Space Environmental Hazards: Radiation, January 31, 1963; 230320 (Box 59)
    - Lectures in Aerospace Medicine, February 1964; 230319 (Box 59)
    - Reprints, Tellus, 1964; 230318 (Box 59)
    - Calcium Filmindicator of Moisture (incomplete), 230317 (Box 59)
    - Simulation of Ring Patterns Observed with Noctilucent Cloud Particles, 230316 (Box 59)
    - A Review of Space Research, 1964; 230315 (Box 59)
    - A Chronology on Science, Technology, and Policy (Index), January-April, June 1965); 230314 (Box 59)
    - A Chronology on Science, Technology and Policy, August 1965; 230313 (Box 59)
    - Mission Requirements of Lifting Systems, Operational Aspects, Volumes 1-2, August 1965; 230312 (Box 59)
    - Mission Requirements of Lifting Systems, Operational Aspects, Volumes 3-4, August 1965; 230311 (Box 60)
    - Preprint: Solar X-Ray Images Obtained Using Grazing Incidence Optics, October 1965; 230310 (Box 60)
    - American Science and Engineering, Inc., Publications:, 230301
      - Program of X-Ray Astronomy to be Performed During Apollo Earth Orbital Flights, Phase II, May 26, 1965; 230309 (Box 60)
      - A Study of X-Ray Sources Outside the Solar System, June 28 and August 11, 1965; 230308 (Box 60)
      - Program of X-Ray Astronomy to be Performed During Apollo Earth Orbital Flight, Second Flight, August 25, 1965; 230307 (Box 60)
      - American Science and Engineering, Inc., Cambridge, Massachusetts (Descriptive Pamphlet, September 1, 1965]; 230306 (Box 60)
      - Proposal to Investigate Rapid Variations of the X-Ray, Flux from Solar Flares..., November 19, 1965; 230305 (Box 60)
      - Rapid Recording of X-Ray Spectra and Images of Solar Flares using a Spectrographic X-Ray Telescope..., December 9, 1965; 230304 (Box 60)
      - Simulation Design Objective for Experiment S-17 on Mission AS-205, March 10, 1966; 230303 (Box 60)
      - U.S. Geological Survey: Surveyor Television Investigations: An Appreciation of the Luna 9 Pictures, March 1966; 230302 (Box 60)
    - Research on Gravitational Mass Sensors, October 1964-April 1966; 230300 (Box 61)
    - Biotechnology at Lockheed Missiles and Space Company, April 1966; 230299 (Box 61)
    - Princeton Advanced Satellite Study, March 1965-May 1966; 230298 (Box 61)
    - Research on Gravitational Mass Sensors, Final Report, October 1964-April 1966; 230297 (Box 61)
    - First Panoramas of the Lunar Surface According to the Material from the Automatic Station Luna-9 (Translated from report of USSR Academy of Sciences, June 29, 1966); 230296 (Box 61)
    - Surveyor 1 Preliminary Results: NASA Five-Day Science Report, June 30, 1966; 230295 (Box 61)
    - A Glancing Incidence Solar Telescope for the Soft X-Ray Region, September 1966; 230294 (Box 61)
    - The Inter-Relationship of Cosmic Ray Anisotropies and the Interplanetary Magnetic Field<, November 1967; 230293 (Box 61)
    - Potential Orbital Facilities for Soft X-Ray and Long Wave Radio Astronomy, December 1967; 230292 (Box 61)
    - Review of Lunar Landing Mission, Part 3, October 6-8, 1967; 230291 (Box 61)
    - Technical Library Materials:, 230285
      - Calcium Metabolism Under Conditions of Weightlessness, June 7, 1963; 230290 (Box 62)
      - Bioastronautics-Slogans, Semantics and Science, June-July, 1964; 230289 (Box 62)
      - Cardiovascular Deconditioning: Role of Blood Volume and Sympathetic Neurohormones, 230288 (Box 62)
      - Relationship Between the Radioemission Flux form Local Source..., October 9, 1967; 230287 (Box 62)
      - Soviet Bloc Research in Geophysics, Astronomy, and Space, April 17, 1968; 230286 (Box 62)
    - ATM HCO [Harvard College Observatory] Man/Machine Interface Review, January 16-17, 1968; 230284 (Box 62)
    - Theoretical Study of the Magnetic Field in the Lunar Wake, January 1968; 230283 (Box 62)
    - Simultaneous Measurements on Three Satellites and the Observation of the Geomagnetic Tail at 1000 R(e), April 1968; 230282 (Box 62)
    - Lunar Explorer 35, May 1968; 230281 (Box 62)
    - Intrinsic Properties of the Lunar Body, May 1968; 230280 (Box 62)
    - Measurements of the Perturbed Interplanetary Magnetic Field in the Lunar Wake, May 1968; 230279 (Box 62)
    - Reprints of Technical Publications:, 230267
      - Time Variation of Sunspot Magnetic Fields, Sept. 1964; 230278 (Box 62)
      - The Solar Wind Velocity and Its Correlation with Geomagnetic, Solar, and Cosmic Ray Activity, August 1965; 230277 (Box 62)
      - Acceleration of Trapped Particles during a Magnetic Storm on 18 April, 1965, July 12, 1967; 230276 (Box 62)
      - Measurements of Gamma-Radiation of the Lunar Surface on the Space Station, August 31, 1967; 230275 (Box 62)
      - Plasma Resonances of the Magnetosphere, September 2, 1967; 230274 (Box 62)
      - Estimates of the Upper Limit of Ion Temperature..., December 29, 1967; 230273 (Box 62)
      - Biological Self Replicating Systems, 1967; 230272 (Box 62)
      - Photoelectron Heating Efficiency in the Ionosphere, February 1, 1968; 230271 (Box 62)
      - Temporal Variations in Geocoronal Balmer Alpha, February 1968; 230270 (Box 62)
      - A Directional, Low-Energy Electron Detector Employing Channel Electron Multipliers, February 28-March 1, 1968; 230269 (Box 62)
      - Theoretical Spectral Scattering of Ice Clouds in the Near-Infrared, August 1968; 230268 (Box 62)
    - Electromagnetic Exploration of the Moon, September 14, 1968; 230266 (Box 62)
    - Proceedings of Winter Study on Uses of Manned Space Flight, December 6-9, 1968; 230265 (Box 63)
    - Live from the Moon, SDC Magazine, July 1969); 230264 (Box 63)
    - The Optical Environment of Manned Spacecraft, undated; 230263 (Box 63)
    - Comparison of Solar Radiation at 34mm and H-Alpha, February 1967; 230262 (Box 63)
    - Translations, two Russian papers:The Solar Wind and Polar Aurorae, And Establishment of a Lunar Unipolar Generator..., 1966, April 1967; 230261 (Box 63)
    - Solar Interplanetary Study Final Report, August 30, 1967; 230260 (Box 63)
    - Papers, Southwest Center for Advanced Studies, Dallas, Texas, 1967-1969:; 230239
      - The Structure of the Thermosphere, November 1967; 230259 (Box 63)
      - The Escape of Atmospheric Helium by Non-Thermal Processes, March 25, 1968; 230258 (Box 63)
      - The Calculation of Multidimensional Repeated Integrals, May 16, 1968; 230257 (Box 63)
      - Calculation of the Dependence of Emitted Light on Charge Density..., May 1968; 230256 (Box 63)
      - Radiative Transfer in an Atmosphere-Ocean System, July 1968; 230255 (Box 63)
      - Radiative-Vibrational Relaxation in Carbon Dioxide, July 1968; 230254 (Box 21)
      - Collisional-Radiative Recombination of Ions and Electrons in High Pressure Plasmas..., August 1968; 230253 (Box 63)
      - Hydrogen and Helium in the Upper Atmosphere, September 1968; 230252 (Box 63)
      - Reinterpretation of Geocoronal Observations with Increased High/Low Altitude Hydrogen Ratio, October 1968; 230251 (Box 63)
      - On Anisotropic Galactic Emissions at Lyman..., October 1968; 230250 (Box 63)
      - Time Dependent Behavior of the A Line in a Low Pressure Helium Afterglow, October 1968; 230249 (Box 63)
      - Thermal Structure of an Alouette II Topside Profile..., January 1969; 230248 (Box 63)
      - Interpretation of Balmer (alpha) Observations of M.F. Ingham, January 1969; 230247 (Box 63)
      - Influence of Electromagnetic Drifts and Neutral Air Winds on Some Features of the F2-Region, March 1969; 230246 (Box 63)
      - Variations of Balmer (alpha) Emission and Related Hydrogen Distributions, May 1969; 230245 (Box 63)
      - The Equivalent Excited State Temperature of a High-Pressure Plasma..., May 1969; 230244 (Box 63)
      - Ion Mass Spectrometer on Explorer XXXI Satellite, n.d.; 230243 (Box 63)
      - Deduction of Ionospheric Parameters from Retarding Potential Analyzers, n.d.; 230242 (Box 63)
      - Environment for Manned Planetary Missions, n.d.; 230241 (Box 63)
      - The Automatic Numerical Evaluation of Definite Integrals, n.d.; 230240 (Box 63)
    - Manned Spacecraft Center Technical Information Program, Computer Searches, August, November 1968; 230238 (Box 63)
  - Subseries P: Oversize Materials, 230204
    - Apollo 8 Commemorative 6-cent U.S. Postage Stamp Album, May 5, 1969; 230236 (Box 64)
    - First-day Issues, sent by correspondent:, 230230
      General note
      [UNK]
      - President Johnson and dogs, card, April 9, 1966; 230235 (Box 64)
      - Honoring U.S. Space Achievements, September 29, 1967; 230234 (Box 64)
      - Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, August and October 1963; 230233 (Box 64)
      - Treaty on Principles Governing the Activities of States in the Exploration and Use of Outer Space, Including the Moon and Other Celestial Bodies, 1967; 230232; 2 copies (Box 64)
      - Letter from Albert Einstein to President F.D. Roosevelt, Concerning Potential for Nuclear Chain Reactions from Uranium, dated August 2, 1939; 230231 (Box 64)
    - Invitation, Program, and Menu for State of Texas Tribute Dinner Honoring the United States Astronauts, December 14, 1969; 230229 (Box 64)
    - 10 photographs from Geology Material [box 10], 230228 (Box 64)
    - 2 unidentified photographs, apparently of lunar terrain, 230227 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers and publications:, 230224
      - Manned Flight Awareness Newsletter, 1968-1969; 230226 (Box 64)
      - CALTECH-Independent Star-News, October 23, 1966; 230225 (Box 64)
    - Foreign newspapers, 230220
      - Alpydubladid (Iceland?), June, July 1967; 230223 (Box 64)
      - Timinn (Iceland?), July 1967; 230222 (Box 64)
      - Morgunbladid (Iceland?), July 1967; 230221 (Box 64)
    - Space Roundup, 1965-1970; 230219 (Box 64)
    - Astronaut Training Film, n.d.; 230218 (Box 65)
    - Sub-subseries 1: Photographs, 230205
      - Photographs of Michel [removed from box 4], 230217 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified Color Slide, 230216 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Michel, Manned Spacecraft Center Official Photographs, 230215 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Manned Spacecraft Center Official Group Photographs, Astronauts:, 230210
        - Group 1 and 2, 230214 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Group 3, 230213 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Group 4 (Scientist-Astronauts), 230212 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Group 5, 230211 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Michel, Various Activities as Scientist-Astronaut, 230209 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - MSFC Michound Assembly Facility, New Orleans, 230208 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous NASA Photographs, 230207 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - AAP Photographs, Equipment Mockups, 230206 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Subseries Q: Memorabilia, 230182
    - NASA ID's and Tags, 230203 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Commemorative Medallions: Lunar Science Conference, Morehead Planetarium, American Fighter Pilots Association, 230202 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Insignia, Tags, and Decals, 230201 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Certificates, 1969; 230200 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Invitations to Launches, 1968, 1973, 1981; 230199 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - First-Day Issues, Apollo 8, 10, 11, 230198 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Commemorative Apollo 11 Medallions, 230197 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Publications and Mementos, 1966-1968; 230196 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Publications and Mementos, 1963-1973; 230195 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Memorabilia, n.d.; 230194 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Plaque, Check-Out T-38 Talon, 230193 (Box 66)
    - Membership Cards, Interstellar Association of Turtles, 230192 (Box 66)
    - Desk sign "F. Curtis Michel", 230191 (Box 66)
    - Two handbooks: Space Data (TRW Systems) and Apollo Block II ECS Components, 230190 (Box 66)
    - Parker lecturer's pointer and pocket tape measure, 230189 (Box 66)
    - Mixed items: ash tray, box of "carnival make-up", pencils, 230188 (Box 66)
    - Monthly Pocket Calendars:, 230184
      - with telephone index and Aeronautical Vest-Pocket Handbook, 1965; 230187 (Box 67)
      - Calnedar, 1966; 230186 (Box 67)
      - Calendars, 1967 and January 1968; 230185 (Box 67)
    - Flight Jacket with NASA Emblem, 230183 (Box 68)
- Series III: Addenda
  - NASA
    - Subseries A: Photographs
      - Photographs File, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Color Photographs (NASA), 1996 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Black and White Photographs, circa 1966 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Black and White Photographs and Negatives, circa 1966 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - NASA Manned Spacecraft Center Official Photographs, 2/1967 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - NASA Concept Art: Space Colony, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Subseries B: Records and Correspondence
      - Contracts: Field Enterprises Educational Corporation, Astronaut-Scientist Agreements, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - NASA Employment Records, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Invitations to Shuttle Launches, 1983-1991 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Subseries C: Flight Plans
      - Incomplete preliminary Flight Plan for AS-204 (aka Apollo I), 1966 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - World Book Encyclopedia
    - Copyrights, Science News and Photographs, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Periodical Clippings
    - 1963-1964 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - 1965 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - 1966 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - 1969 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - 1970-1989 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - undated (Box 69, Folder 19)